<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Book-A-Meal</string>
    <string name="slogan">We transport products to customers quickly with no defaults
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tracking_order">TrackingOrder</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_admin">MainAdminActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">About Book-A-Meal</string>
    <string name="staff_text">
        "Book a meal is the future of food delivery in the world
The best part of online meal booking facility is that a restaurant meal can be booked as per the convenience of the guest without visiting the actual restaurant location. Before booking the meal you get a chance to see the clear pictures of the restaurant menu and the meal which you want to book.
The detailed information about restaurant, other services and reviews help the new booker to get an idea about the restaurant for meal booking.

Online booking service is the best way to book a meal in any destination in the area, Get takeout, or choose delivery when available. With this online booking service customer can book meal which is near location of your residence or work place and choose the meal from restaurant menu. Many good restaurants which provide the online food booking facility are online on the website. In online booking you can save time and amount of money due to the discount rates offered to the agencies, by the restaurant. These online agencies usually make consensus with many restaurant. The restaurant provides substantial discounts to the agencies and in return these agencies make block booking for the restaurant. The discounts provided by the restaurant are passed on to the customers.

The procedure to make an online meal booking is very simple. The customer should choose an restaurant on our websites and here are many restaurants are defined from all over the world, Get takeout, or choose delivery when available. Now in second step go through the list of different restaurants available in a particular city. The site contains names, amenities, taxes, tariff and all other related information of the restaurant. Once customer selects the restaurant, heshe needs to give relevant information, such as customer's name, type of meal, detail address, menu title and any other additional requests, to the restaurant. Before final confirmation of the restaurant which menu item is having or not, it is important to check that all details are correct or not. Once online meal book is confirmed, pack your bags for pleasure or meal is finding you Get takeout, or choose delivery when available."



    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_scrolling">About Book-A-Meal</string>
    <string name="admin_text">
       "Book a meal is the future of food delivery in the world
The best part of online meal booking facility is that a restaurant meal can be booked as per the convenience of the guest without visiting the actual restaurant location. Before booking the meal you get a chance to see the clear pictures of the restaurant menu and the meal which you want to book.
The detailed information about restaurant, other services and reviews help the new booker to get an idea about the restaurant for meal booking.

Online booking service is the best way to book a meal in any destination in the area, Get takeout, or choose delivery when available. With this online booking service customer can book meal which is near location of your residence or work place and choose the meal from restaurant menu. Many good restaurants which provide the online food booking facility are online on the website. In online booking you can save time and amount of money due to the discount rates offered to the agencies, by the restaurant. These online agencies usually make consensus with many restaurant. The restaurant provides substantial discounts to the agencies and in return these agencies make block booking for the restaurant. The discounts provided by the restaurant are passed on to the customers.

The procedure to make an online meal booking is very simple. The customer should choose an restaurant on our websites and here are many restaurants are defined from all over the world, Get takeout, or choose delivery when available. Now in second step go through the list of different restaurants available in a particular city. The site contains names, amenities, taxes, tariff and all other related information of the restaurant. Once customer selects the restaurant, heshe needs to give relevant information, such as customer's name, type of meal, detail address, menu title and any other additional requests, to the restaurant. Before final confirmation of the restaurant which menu item is having or not, it is important to check that all details are correct or not. Once online meal book is confirmed, pack your bags for pleasure or meal is finding you Get takeout, or choose delivery when available."

    </string>
    <string name="sign_in_as_staff">Sign In As Staff</string>
    <string name="sign_in_as_admin">Sign In As Admin</string>
</resources>
